Class of 1964 Records, 1960-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1964 Records
1960-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1964.
RG 80 UUID:7abec009-a479-4af7-8cdc-1f643ab1a11c
2 boxes (.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1964.
The Class of 1964 was the eighty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1964 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1964, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1964 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 2)
- Commencement Speaker 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 3)
- Freshman Handbook 1960-1961 (Box 2231, Folder 4)
- General 1963-1964 (Box 2231, Folder 5)
- Groups 1960-1964 (Box 2231, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day 1964 (Box 2231, Folder 8)
- Class Letters 1966-1976 (Box 2231, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 2231, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 2231, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1979, 1984, 1999 (Box 2231, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 2231, Folder 13)
- Reunions-25th Reunion Book 1989 (Box 2231, Folder 14)
- Reunions 2004 (Box 2231, Folder 15)
- Who's Who 1960 (Box 2231, Folder 16)